<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Personal Page</title>
    <link>https://voosterveen.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Personal Page</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    
	<atom:link href="https://voosterveen.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://voosterveen.github.io/cven.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://voosterveen.github.io/cven.html</guid>
      <description>CV Vera Oosterveen    Vera Oosterveen Stats and Data Enthusiast  v.oosterveen@gmail.com 06 50 49 47 52 voosterveen.github.io/ linkedin.com/in/voosterveen github.com/voosterveen   Education MSc in Methodology and Statistics for the Behavioural, Biomedical and Social Sciences Utrecht University 2018 - present  BSc in Sociology Utrecht University 2013 - 2016    Skills &amp;amp; Proficiency - Python - Research - Tutoring  - R - Statistical Analysis - Teaching      Other: Shiny, MPlus, SPSS, Git, Markdown, JAGS    Experiences Research Intern 2019 - present  Statistics Netherlands, The Hague  Master thesis: Detecting incorrect labels in a business register using text classiﬁcation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://voosterveen.github.io/cvnl.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://voosterveen.github.io/cvnl.html</guid>
      <description>CV Vera Oosterveen    Vera Oosterveen Statistiek en Data Fan  v.oosterveen@gmail.com 06 50 49 47 52 voosterveen.github.io/ linkedin.com/in/voosterveen github.com/voosterveen   Educatie MSc in Methodology and Statistics for the Behavioural, Biomedical and Social Sciences Universiteit Utrecht 2018 - heden  BSc in Sociologie Universiteit Utrecht 2013 - 2016    Skills - Python - Onderzoek - Studiebegeleiding  - R - Statistische analyses - Les geven      Overig: Shiny, MPlus, SPSS, Git, Markdown, JAGS    Ervaring Onderzoeksstagair 2019 - heden  Centraal Bureau voor de Statistiek, Den Haag  Master scriptie: Detecting incorrect labels in a business register using text classiﬁcation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://voosterveen.github.io/about.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://voosterveen.github.io/about.html</guid>
      <description>During my bachelor in Sociology I discovered my interest for methods and statistics. That is why I started the master programme Methodology and Statistics for the Behavioural, Biomedical and Social Sciences. Within the programme there is the opportunity to enrol in the European Master in Official Statistics, which I did. Currently, I am writing my thesis at Statistics Netherlands (in Dutch: Centraal Bureau voor de Statistiek).
Next to studying, I am working freelance as a statistics tutor.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>